greyhound.com 2015-06-06

# Greyhound.com | Privacy Policy

As a valued Customer, you are entitled to your personal privacy. With that in mind, Greyhound has adopted a Privacy Policy (“Policy”) which explains and confirms our commitment to provide you with a variety of travel services while maintaining your personal privacy.

###  Sharing & Disclosure of Personal Information

Greyhound will never sell your personal or financial information to any third party. Your personal and/or financial information, however, may be shared with third parties, who are authorized by Greyhound for the following purposes: 

  * Credit card verification, processing and fraud detection purposes as part of your ticket purchase; and/or  

  * Legal disclosure to a governmental agency, law enforcement or court as required by law in the good faith belief that disclosure is necessary or advisable.

Greyhound uses third party payment processing companies to bill you for goods and services, or for other purposes within the ordinary course of business. We make these companies commit to contract (1) to provide protections for your personally identifiable information that are no less protective than those set out in this Policy, and (2) to use your personally identifying information only for the purposes for which the third party has been engaged by Greyhound. Greyhound is not liable for the acts or omissions of these third parties except to the extent required by applicable law. 

In addition, if you decide to participate in our marketing programs (including but not limited to customer loyalty, incentives, affinity, promotions or contests), your non-financial personal information may be released to reputable third parties in order to fulfill certain business requirements of those programs.  
We may also share information that we collect in the aggregate with third parties, including, without limitation, our marketing partners. 

###  Personal Information Collected For Processing Transactions

Greyhound collects personal information (name, address, phone number, etc.) as well as a credit card number to process transactions. An e-mail address for an online purchase is optional; however, your e-mail address is required for Print at Home purchases and if you would like a copy of your confirmation statement e-mailed to you. We use the information we collect during the purchase process for billing purposes, to fill your orders, for administrative, analytical, correspondence, and operational purposes, to customize advertisements and offers and for other marketing purposes, and for other purposes discussed in this Policy.

###  Marketing Programs

Greyhound collects personal information including email addresses and telephone numbers to facilitate our marketing programs and communicate with customers who have expressed an interest in upcoming specials, discounts, and helpful travel tips. Often this information is collected on web sites that are hosted by companies associated with Greyhound. Unless you choose to opt-in, your information will not be shared.

By participating in our marketing programs, you agree to honor and abide by the rules and regulations contained therein. Please read all rules before participating.

Greyhound takes no responsibility for the specific privacy rules or terms and conditions of the contest sponsors or other third parties and we encourage you to examine the privacy policies contained on these sites.

Road Rewards Program  
If you do not already have a Road Rewards account, you can easily establish one by visiting our website. Electing to establish a Road Rewards account will enroll you in the Greyhound frequent rider program and give you the opportunity to earn rewards. You will not be able to earn points toward reward trips if you elect to not sign up for this program. As a Road Rewards Member, you may also receive special offers by e-mail simply for being a Member of the Road Rewards program.

We may use the personally identifiable information you provide when you become a Road Rewards Member for analytical, administrative, marketing, correspondence or other operational or business purposes. For more information on how we may use your personally identifiable information as a Road Rewards Member, please see our **Customer Communications** section below. 

###  Customer Communications

Post Purchase E-mail Communication  
When you make a travel reservation with us and you provide your e-mail address during the purchase process, we may send you trip-related emails, including, without limitation, emails that (a) confirm the details of your purchase, (b) describe service-related information in connection with your reservation or to inform you of upgrades or product enhancements related to your purchase, (c) request feedback on our services and/or your specific travel experiences, or (d) include special offers for products or services from Greyhound or our marketing partners related to your trip. 

E-mail Promotions, Offers, and Updates  
You may receive e-mail communications from us which may include special offers, Road Rewards information or similar offerings. You may opt-out of receiving these messages at any time by selecting “unsubscribe” from any email communication.

As a Member of the Road Rewards program, you may receive Road Rewards e-mail communications, which may include program news and special offers, either during the Road Rewards enrollment process or from your Road Rewards account preferences web page. During enrollment, the default option is to receive both Road Rewards e-mail products. If you are not interested in receiving these messages with special Members-only news and offers, the boxes should be unchecked prior to submitting the enrollment form. You may also opt-out of receiving these messages at any time by adjusting your preferences through the account preferences webpage. 

Account Information  
We currently send non-promotional e-mails to our Road Rewards Members containing account and award status notifications, to notify Members of program updates, and to communicate other program-related information. 

Customer Feedback  
We like to hear from our Customers and encourage you to e-mail us your comments, questions or other feedback. By submitting such information along with your e-mail address, you consent to receiving e-mail from us in response to your feedback or question. 

Contests & Surveys  
We may occasionally offer users the opportunity to participate in surveys or contests on our web site. 

If we have your e-mail address, we may also send you surveys or contest invitations by e-mail. We may have your e-mail address if:  

  * You have made a purchase on our web site and provided your e-mail address during the purchase process;
  * You have set up a Road Rewards account and provided your e-mail address either during the registration process or when updating your account information;
  * You provide a friend’s e-mail address when you refer the friend to one of our web pages; or
  * We have received your e-mail address by any other means.

If you choose to participate in a contest or survey, we may request certain personally identifiable information from you. This information may include contact information (such as name, e-mail address, phone number, and shipping address) and optional demographic information (such as your age and gender).

Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. We may use this information to administer the contest or survey (e.g., notify contest winners, award prizes, and update participant’s profiles). We may also use this information to improve the web site experience for our Customers, to improve our product or service offerings, or for other internal business uses.

We may use third party service providers to conduct these surveys or contests. These companies are prohibited from using our users’ personally identifiable information for any other purpose. These third parties are bound by contract to Greyhound to use adequate security measures to protect your personal information.

Forward-to-a-Friend and Refer-a-Friend  
You may use a referral feature (either on a web page, in an e-mail, from a banner ad or other communication) to inform a friend about a Greyhound web page or promotion. Greyhound may use any e-mail address provided when using this referral feature to send an e-mail on your behalf to such designated recipients about the particular promotion, product, or service in which you indicated your "friend" may have an interest. 

Site Usage Profile  
We store and use certain personally identifiable information and information that we collect through cookies and log files to create a site usage profile of your preferences. We may use this information to provide you with targeted advertisements and offers on our web site. In addition we may provide this information to our select marketing platforms, and these cookies may be used for targeted online advertising by both Greyhound and third party merchants on third party websites. 

###  Personal Information Concerning Children Under 13

Greyhound's website is not directed at children under the age of 13. Accordingly, Greyhound does not want and people should not submit personal information concerning anyone under age 13.

###  Non-Personally-Identifiable Information We Collect

In some cases, Greyhound may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. Examples of this type of information include, but are not limited to the frequency of your use of this web site and the route by which you choose to access it, and your use of any hyperlinks available on this web site. We and our service providers or agents may process and use this data for purposes including, but not limited to planning web site development, assessing patterns of use, planning and assessing marketing initiatives by Greyhound. This information is gathered by certain tools and methods such as the collection of your IP address or the use of cookies. 

  * IP Addresses  
An Internet Protocol ("IP") address is a numeric code, for example, "152.163.207.197." This code is used to communicate between your Internet service provider and the World Wide Web. An IP address does not identify you individually. Greyhound logs inbound IP addresses to administer our website and to aggregate information on site traffic for internal use.
  * Cookies  
Cookies (and similar files such as single pixel GIF’s, web beacons or tags) are small computer files written to your computer when you visit websites. You have the option of setting your browser to refuse Cookies. To utilize all promotional offers and discounts on Greyhound.com you need to allow temporary "session cookies" that will go away when your browser is closed. No personal or credit card information is collected by any Greyhound Cookies.

Greyhound Cookies collect anonymous, non-personal information to make your use of the web site easier and to allow Greyhound to track and improve the effectiveness of our on-line advertising. For example, when you check the appropriate box a Greyhound Cookie will remember your origination and destination locations.

Greyhound also works with on-line advertising agencies to sell Greyhound's services. These agencies use Cookies to track which Greyhound ads you have seen and the amounts you spend on Greyhound.com so that we may effectively market to consumers.

###  Opt-Out Policy

You have the option of being excluded from the various marketing contact lists by opting out at any time. Opt-out requests for contests, however, must be received within the duration of the contest to be removed from that contest. To stop messages coming to your cell phone, just reply "STOP."

To opt out, update or change any contact information send us an e-mail to [webmaster@greyhound.com](mailto:webmaster@greyhound.com) with your name, e-mail address and mailing address.

###  Security

Greyhound takes precautions to protect your personal and credit card information from misuse or unauthorized disclosure. For example, Greyhound uses encryption software from VeriSign, the industry leader in secure site software technologies, to protect your information.

Look for the "s" after "http" in the address line of your browser. This indicates that the information sent from your computer to Greyhound.com is encrypted using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

###  Links to Other Websites

While we strive to partner with reputable firms, Greyhound takes no responsibility for any content, information collected, terms and conditions or privacy rules maintained on any linked site and we strongly encourage you to examine the privacy policies contained on these sites. Please inform us at [webmaster@greyhound.com](mailto:webmaster@greyhound.com) about any concerns you may have regarding any of our linked sites.

###  Application of Policy

This Policy is applicable to Greyhound and its affiliates, including without limitation Greyhound (U.S., Canada and Mexico), BoltBus, Greyhound Package Express (U.S. and Canada), Valley Transit, Greyhound Express (U.S. and Canada), Greyhound Connect, Lucky Streak, NeOn, Yo! Bus, Road Rewards and QuickLink, and all official Greyhound offerings, divisions and departments, including without limitation Fare and Scheduling, Passenger Call Center, Marketing, Customer Relations/Service, Road Rewards, and our mobile applications. Certain affiliated Greyhound websites may also have additional privacy policies and procedures in place, as described on those websites.

###  Consent

Your use of Greyhound's website, services and participation in our marketing programs is your express consent for Greyhound to use your personal information as described above. We reserve the right to make changes to this Policy from time to time, and for this reason, we encourage you to review the Policy posted at [Greyhound.com](https://www.greyhound.com/) periodically.

###  Changes in Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is current as of the effective date set forth below. Greyhound reserves the right to change this privacy policy from time to time consistent with applicable privacy laws and principles. If we make changes to this Policy, we will notify you by publication here.

###  Contact Us

If you have any questions about the use of your personal information or would like to correct or amend any personal information we maintain about you, please feel free to contact us at [webmaster@greyhound.com](mailto:webmaster@greyhound.com), or send a letter to: 

Greyhound Lines, Inc.  
IT Webmaster/MS850  
P.O. Box 660362  
Dallas, TX 75266-0362

June 2013
